Oh, good evening. Oh, no, no, no.
Nogizaka46min TV
Thank you very much. Good evening, everyone. I'm Asuka Saito. It's been a while.
It's May now, and it's a bit noisy. A lot.
We are having rehearsals for Asuka Saito's graduation concert to be held on May 17 and 18,
After the rehearsal, everyone is around right now,
Recently, I wonder if all of you have seen the short YouTube video of me being assaulted by junior members on YouTube.
Today, I would like to do the opposite,
I am going to storm into this lively group of children.
I'm going.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, I only have one.
coy, coy, coy.
Orenso orenso.
Go get me the bricks.
Go get me a brick.
I'll be bullied when I come back after a long time
They want me to go get them.
What the hell is this?
What are you doing?
It's so crowded.
I'll be waiting for you with a game of Friendship.
You guys rehearsed together today, right?
How much energy do you have?
How much stamina do you have? You're doing great.
You're doing great.
How are you?
I'm great.
Great.
We had a full rehearsal today, right?
Yesterday and today.
Are you tired? This setlist is...
So much?
But it's fun.
Really?
Really? I'm happy.
How's it going?
What about you, Black?
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
He said he was nervous.
Why are you wearing glasses?
Are you a little...
Are they real glasses?
Real glasses.
That's right.
I see Asuka and her a lot.
Of course.
For example, 3rd term students and 4th term students too.
but also 5th term students see Asuka-san at least once.
That makes me very happy.
Really?
Grin, grin, grin, grin, grin.
She's always smiling at me.
Kuromi does.
Asuka-san knows me too.
She grins at me.
I'm sorry, I might be mistaken.
I'm sorry.
Thank you... you think so.
Then, what about you?
Yes.
I was so happy to see Asuka's performance up close.
Why?
Because you give great performances in various places,
But won't this be the last time? At the Dome concert.
So the setlist will be different for the two days.
Totally different.
So, I'm going to steal all of Asuka's performance in all the songs,
That's nice.
I wanted to finish the show,
I'm getting a blade in my fangs.
That's great.
You're doing well, aren't you? Lately.
You're doing well?
I'm doing well.
I'm happy.
Really?
Admit it.Admit it.
I'm glad.
I'm glad you guys are enjoying what you're doing.
But say something tough.
I understand.
I'm the one who hates hard things the most.
That's why.
I can't say it even if I wanted to.
I'm a junior now, and I can't say even if I wanted to.
So, please tell me. If there is something you don't like.
I don't.
Really?
No, I don't.
Are you shy?
I thought it was just for a moment.
I'm sure it's because I'm in front of you all.
That's right.
It's just the thought that your fans are watching you.
I'm sure.
I'm getting a little shy.
I'm a little shy.
Yeah.
It's so lively.
I'm sorry, I'm just a little bit nervous.
I'm sorry.
I can afford it.
I'm so busy.
Well, goodbye.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
How did you do that thing with the delivery?
Maybe we can do it at least a little bit taller.
That's right.
Is that right?
This is good.
Really?
Thank you.
You're all still here.
There's a lot of us.
Well, keep hornation going.
Hornation.
Just a little pull.
Don't run.
Thank you.
Hello.
Good work.
What are you doing? With everyone.
I was just watching YouTube.
YouTube?
There was a short video of me giving Asuka a piggyback ride today.
You're really watching it.
I was watching it.
You're really watching.
I'm really watching.
You were on your back.
I was amazing, wasn't I?
A piggyback.
I thought it was absolutely impossible.
I knew it.
I'm so muscular.
You were able to do it.
Yes, I could do it.
You're doing it. Lately.
I'm doing it to put Asuka on the page.
Without sleeping.
Please.
Okay?
I'll give you a better piggyback ride.
Better than me.
It's safe and secure now.
Can I ask you to do it?
Why?Why?
What's the use of a piggyback?
It's not safe.
I want you to rewatch it.
Re-watch.
Here?
Yes. May I?
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Good luck.
You're safe.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
It's really safe.
Are you that strong?
I just put Yakubo-chan on it and drove around.
I've practiced.
I also carried Kaede around.
Really?
I practiced twice, so I'm fine.
Then you must be losing energy.
I'm sure it's wearing you down.
Are you sure you're okay?
Really, I'm fine.
I'm fine. It's just my legs and back.
I don't want to.
Because, you know, you won't have any hiccups with this, will you?
No, it won't.
Just take care of yourself.
Just take care of your legs and hips.
They're super strong.
Your legs and feet are in shape and strong.
Take care of yourself.
Don't hurt yourself.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm really fine.
Ready?
Okay.
You really need to get your hands tight.
This position is the hardest.
Okay. Here I go.
Ready.
Nice!
It sure feels safe.
I'll take you home.
It's stable.
You can go home.
Great!
It's stable!
Can you keep going? This delivery.
I know, right? Me too.
Thank you.
It's going to be okay.
It's all right, isn't it?
Of course I am.
Bend over.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to bother you.
But of course, I'm here.
No, it's just me now,
What?
It's so natural.
Because, you know? Aseyama.
You're the only one laughing.
I'm the only one among the four of us.
What? It's true.
I'm so embarrassed.
Why are we gathered like this?
It's a mystery.
It's been so long since I've done this kind of distribution,
I forgot how to do it. I forgot how to do it.
But it's perfect.
So far, it's a perfect score of 100 million.
You're flimsy.
Flimsy human being.
Wait a minute.
Hold off.
Because this character reverse is not funny.
Look at the four of them.
How's the rehearsal going? How's the rehearsal going?How are things going? How are the rehearsals going?
Is everyone feeling good about it?
Do you think it's going well?
I'm tired.
They're starting to make out.
Let's ask here, too.
What do you think of the set list?
Is it hard? Is it hard?
Not at all. It's fun. It's all right.
They're all good songs. They're all skateboarding songs.
They're good kids.
I'm glad.
I think they're going to have fun.
Hey, Nyana.
Natchu. Natty.
Thank you.
Yama, I'm going to ask you to do a lot of things for me.
I'll do my best.
Did you watch this?
I was watching it.
What did I do? Yuna's.
I took some pictures together to make memories.
Huh? Where is that picture?
You haven't developed them yet, have you?
I'll send them to you. I'll send it to you when it's developed.
But I was so nervous.
What? Why?
It was at the beginning of the rehearsal when you were going to meet Asuka, wasn't it?
That's right. I took the picture at the beginning of the rehearsal.
It's a little stiff, isn't it? That was me.
It was a little stiff.
Here you go.
Okay, then,
I'm in the middle.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Let's end with a little gathering.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Don't push me on camera.
I want to see everyone.
Turn around.
What's going on?
Thank you.
I'm going.
I'll see you later.
It's good to see you again.
What is this?
Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
I'll get hit.
Hello.
It's late coming in.
Let's do it.
We're all done rehearsing.
What?
Oh, no.
I've calmed down.
I can't help but wonder...
What are you doing?
We were just talking.
We were promoting each other's goods.
They advertised each other's goods, and this is what they got.
They were promoting each other's products.
Like, "This is good.
Eh.... Good night.
I want this the most.
Ehh.
This is just for practicality.
It's really nice.
When I see Asuka in the morning,
I always have this.
Asuka always has this when she comes out of the elevator.
I thought it's practical.
It's practical.
What's this?
This has Asuka printed on it.
It's true.
Look at her face.
Yuri?Yuri?
It's so cute.
Since when did you learn that? That's not it.
Look at this.
Then watch this. Yuri.
Okay, I'll take a look.
What's this?
It's Paul.
I know it when I see it.
Yes, I know.
Isn't he cute?
He's cute, isn't he?
It's cute.
It's nice.
It's like nothing I've ever seen before.
Stylish, right?
Yes, it is.
That sound.
Practical, right?
It's really good.
I can use it during rehearsals.
A notepad, a chart of where to stand at rehearsals, and so on.
Sure. Will you use it?
Of course I will.
Really? You'll use it?
Of course I would.
You don't use a notepad, do you?
Yes, I do.
You will?
You'll need to write it down by the day of the show,
Final stage. Notes.
I see.
A surprise on the last page.
Yes, that's right.
It's difficult.
The content is a secret, right?
Secret?
All of it.
All of it?
I don't mean all of it,
He's going to explain it to us.
Is it a secret that you have some tricks up your sleeve?
I've already told you that.
I told you.
It's a secret.
I don't need to worry about the gimmick.
I wrote a message.
I love your handwriting.
It's so beautiful.
Really?
It's cute.
It's beautiful.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to come across as a water killer,
I'm so embarrassed.
That's not good.
But I'm glad. I'm glad you guys are using me in rehearsal.
They're even better.
It's nice.
This is a tote bag.
Yes, it is,
It's cute.
And the frontage is quite wide,
Yes, it is. It can hold a lot.
I think it will fit two days or so with plenty of room to spare,
I think it can be used in summer, fall, and winter.
It's nice. It's good.
Yes, it is. I've been practicing a little.
When did you practice?
Thank you.
I see.
I think I can do that,
Like Anpa,
What?
You can put another one on top of it.
Me?
I thought it might work.
I'm saying this,
It has a wide opening, so I think it can hold anything,It's a pretty wide frontage, so I think anything goes in there,
I'm pretty happy. I have everything.
Guess what?
I have everything.
What?
What do you think?
Oh, shit. Time's up.
Did you say that?
I'm putting a happy smiley face in there.
Thank you.
Please, someone retrieve it.
You're not very smooth.
Really. When I talk to Yumekin,
I can't understand what he's saying in Japanese.
And before I ask him what he's packing,
He almost said "happy" before I asked him what he was packing.
You were saying that a little bit, weren't you?
He's too smooth,
There is a song about being self-centered, isn't there?
I wanted to write it down once,
I wrote "Let's go with self-centeredness,
But when I looked back at it, it says "Let's go with self-centeredness.
It might be a little scary.
What?
You're not smooth.
I don't have a bad tongue.
My earthly tongue is bad, too.
In Japanese.
I'm scared.
You're scary.
That's all.
Was I scary? Just now.
That's all. I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
Thank you.
You're scary.
I'm not scared.
It's a bird doll.
It's cute. It looks good on you.
It looks good on you.
Really?
I was just talking with some of the students in my first semester, and they were all excited,
They said I was cute,
It's cute.
I feel like a fish in an aquarium.
That's a good one.
It's a bird doll with a tall nose.
It has a beautiful nose. The nose is so beautiful.
It's cute.
It looks good on me.
If I wear this, I'll be popular.
I'm sure you would.
Asuka, please wear it.
I was so surprised.
They're really serious.
This team is.
You had a meeting? Everyone.
That's amazing.
This is really hard to do.
It's like nothing I've ever seen before.
It's true.
It's normal when it's covered in blood.
Cute.
Thank you for your hard work.
So cute!
They look good all over the world.
Akane looks the best.
Her fins are the best.
She looks like a grandchild.
I feel like a grandchild.
I'm going home now!
So cute!
That's enough.
I'm going to get some air.
It's getting hot.It's getting hotter.
I guess a lot of things are coming.
This is coming.
It cools you down and makes you groan, but it also exercises your bad toxins.
It cools and growls, but it also exercises bad toxins.
This is cute.
It has an ego,
It growls sometimes.
I was thinking that maybe it's a reference to this Ar.
Really?
It growled about once every three times.
Is that what it's supposed to do?
What are you saying?
What do you mean?
Suddenly his ego comes out and he gets angry.
He's saying it's going to take a miracle.
I think he's got it in him.
He says he's going to stop at his hand.
What's that?
Ah.
I like it.
Funky is better.
Ah.
It's not working.
You're cute.
What is it?
What is it? You guys.
Oh, my God.
Please buy one.
Oh, do you have the current one?
The current one.
The current one?
I see.
It's quite a surprise.
I'm sure you'll enjoy this.
I'm tired all at once. These people.
I'm sorry.
Wow. It's so lively.
Thank you.
Thank you for waiting.
I'm going to go now.
Please take care of the goods, everyone.
Please buy them.
Bye bye.
I'm tired.
Oh, you're going home.
Hello.
Are you practicing?
I'm practicing.
That's great.
Gather around!
Okay, I'll meet you there.
It's close.
It's close. A little bit.
How's it going? How are you guys doing? Rehearsal.
How's it going?
We're good.
But is this your first time at Tokyo Dome?
It's our first time.
Are you nervous? Are you looking forward to it?
I saw it once on a live stream.
Did you?
I probably watched the finals of JETS two years ago at the graduation ceremony for Ms. Takayama.
Are you looking forward to it?
I am looking forward to it.
It's sad.
Sad?
I am sad.
Why?
I'm going away.
I see.
Thank you.
How about you?
Is it me?
Coming out?
You're not sitting down?
There's no sit.
Can I say something funny?Can I say something funny?
What?
You often say it's the size of the Tokyo Dome.
Yes, that's right. I say it, I say it, I say it.
So I'm happy to be there.
That's for sure.
It's not strange at all.
I'm often told I'm saying strange things.
It's always the same.
Sure, sure.
Then I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
Who are you leaving it for?
I've never left an entire Tokyo Dome before.
What's he saying? Now.
I've never been to a place that's the size of the Tokyo Dome.
That's all I'm saying.
So, Iroha?
Yes, Iroha.
How's it going?
I don't know. It's a big place.
I run a lot and get tired even after rehearsals,
But when I see Asuka's face,
You were following me now, weren't you?
What?
Seeing your face heals me.
That's a lie.
I can do my best.
Really?
I'm serious.
Are you enjoying it? The setlist itself.
It's a lot of fun.
Really? I'm glad.
Everyone says so.
Thank you.
Well, Shokichi.
Shokichi?
Yes, that's right. But you haven't seen Asuka-san in a while, right?
So it's not the first time, right?
When I saw Asuka's face after a long time at the rehearsal,
I reacted as if I met her for the first time,
Asuka-san is cute.
On the first day of rehearsal, I only saw Asuka's face rather than rehearsal.
What?
Really?
Because you didn't talk.
I got nervous with everyone.
What?
I'm glad.
Thank you.
Well, let's hear it. A lot.
Then, do you have a lot?
I often get close to Asuka-san in various songs in the band,
I always look at Asuka's face during rehearsal.
You were looking at me a lot today, weren't you?
Not only today.
You were watching her all the time?
All the time.
I've been watching since the day of the confirmation rehearsal.
I thought Asuka was looking at both sides of the audience from both sides.
I felt sad.
Sad, isn't it?
But you want to burn Asuka in your eyes, don't you?
Are you that type of person?
Very much so.
Is that so?
That's right.
I'm still looking at him like I don't care about his eyelids.
I'm scared.
What? What is it?
No.
Thank you.
Really.
Are you happy?Are you happy?
It's a little hot.
You don't smile.
Thanks.
I really love it.
I'll do my best.
So, Tere-san, do you want to talk too?
Last time, you made a short video with Asuka on YouTube,
When they come back, they all have a melancholy look on their faces.
What's that?
Asuka-san has made them feel like they've been boned.
That's right,
What's that?
I went there too, and Asuka made me fall in love with her.
I'm scared.
Everyone's eyes would be like hearts in their eyes.
I didn't do that, did I? Me.
No, I'm wearing the T-shirt Asuka signed for me.
A bear?
You're making him wear it?
A bear.
I have a big bear doll,
Oh, really?
Put it on.
The one with the flying bird.
Yes, that's it.
Thank you.
They're looking at the other kids.
I do.
Thank you.
You're the one who's asleep.
You saw that, right? You did something weird.
You did?
He saw you.
I couldn't get rid of the smell for three days,
I couldn't get away from it.
Really.
I really did.
The smell wants to live here.
But you might understand.
But everyone told me they envied me.
Why?
What do you mean they're jealous of that?
No, you can't.
You can have my feet.
You didn't make it either.
Of course not.
Next time, you can have my leg.
You sure? Are you sure?
What about you, Mao?
Today, I..,
I was between Arno and Asuka-san,
I kept looking at Asuka-san who was coming for me,
I thought she was coming, so I told her I was coming,
I told her to go, but she kept looking over there,
I said, "Let's go," but she kept looking over there. She was looking this way.
I won.
No, I didn't.
Because the pressure was too much,
I got you.
I've got eyes in my head.
Call me early in the game.
Thank you.
Okay, I'll let you guys know.
But I was just in the middle of a delivery,
I hugged you.
I couldn't get the smell out of my mouth either,
I can smell the rest of it now.
No way!
Asuka was here.
I'm trying to do something.
One thing I want to say,
I talked with Asuka-san and she said she doesn't cry anymore.
That's true.
At first, I used to cry just by looking at her,
But I'm fine now.
That's true.
Is that good?
We actually worked together,We actually worked together,
I thought, "Surprisingly, this guy is not a big deal,
I thought he wasn't that great.
Is that what you're saying?
No, that's not it.
It's a sign that we've grown a little closer.
Nice word.
Cute.
That's a cute one.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
Okay, Ms. Sakira.
Asuka-san from Fact One,
Asuka-san from Fact One looked at Aya in a really kind way,
There?
That's it.
I always look forward to seeing her smile.
I always look forward to seeing her smiling face.
So that's it.
I didn't know there was such a way to sleep.
Thank you.
But I'm going to ask you to do a lot of work, too.
Why?
I want to do my best.
Thank you very much.
What's the last thing?
I get nervous when you say "last".
Aya's eyes are a little moist right now.
You're kidding?
Did I give it away?
You did?
She's cute.
Cute.
You're not so bad,
Why not?
Why?
I'm not crying.
You're crying.
You're cute.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
It's nothing. It's nothing.
You're cute.
What's wrong?
What are those tears for? Oh, my God.
Don't worry about it.
I do care.
I don't know what to do.
What's wrong?
You're crying so hard.
I'm not crying.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Really?
I don't mind if it ends like this.
No, I can't.
Really? Are you sure?
I'm fine.
I'll ask you later.
You're so cute.
Then let's listen to Nagi's story without worrying about it.
But that's exactly why I also made a video with Mr. Yasuzuka,
We really met,
It's been a while since we met,
It was almost time, wasn't it?
That's right. It was right after that.
I was so nervous,
I was so nervous that I was embarrassed to look back at the video and be embarrassed myself.
No kidding? Was it really like that?
For such a short period of time, you made me do some amazing things.
I wanted him to do it. I wanted him to do it.
But now, I can talk with less nervousness than I did then.
Really?
I'm glad.
Because you were teaching me how to pretend to be wrong earlier.Because you taught me how to pretend to be wrong earlier.
I'm going to hold that kind of thing in my heart.
I embarrassed myself at the TOHKEN rehearsal.
I won't forget it. Me.
Thank you. Everyone.
That's great. I've heard so many stories. I've heard so many stories.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
But..,
But... since a while ago...
I was wondering why Umezawa wasn't here.
Huh?
Where is he?
Mr. Umezawa is upstairs.
Oh, Umezawa?
Okay, you mind? You're welcome to come with me.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's go.
You were asking me the other day how to get better at dancing,
I watched it today,
I was saying that you should imitate someone who dances like you do,
Wait a minute. I'm embarrassed.
I'm going to say it all here for now.
I'm a little embarrassed.
But after seeing it today, I want to imitate you.
I do? Really?
I'm glad.
Yes, I am.
I'm glad. Thank you.
But you didn't see it.
I'll look at it.
Wait a minute. What's going on?
Wait a minute.
What? Wait a minute. If I'm not mistaken,
I think the time has stopped.
Wait a minute. Is time frozen?
Hasn't time stood still?
I keep seeing this guy everywhere I go.
What? Wait a minute.
Time stands still.
Because.
Wait a minute.
What is this?
Did we all just freeze?
Wait a minute.
He's gonna laugh.
He's strong.
His eyebrows.
I'm sorry.
I've been at it a long time.
Thank you. Hey, guys.
Wait.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's great.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Good for you.
Thank you, guys.
What do you mean, "good"?
I didn't think I'd make it back today.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you so much for making it all so festive.
Shall we go upstairs?
Upstairs.
What's up there? Show us the way.
I'm going to make my face so small.
It's so small, it's already small.
Look in the mirror.
Your tupperware is amazing.
It's really eye-catching.
Thank you very much.
Good luck at the dance.
I'll do my best.
Oh, oh, there you are, guys.
Yo.
Wait a minute.Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
What?
Something's connected.
Wait a minute.
No way.
What? I'm scared.
What? This place is frozen in time, too.
Wait a minute.
Hey!
Welcome back.
How can I help you? How can I help you?
Asuka?
What? What's that look?
Welcome back.
Welcome back. Thanks for your hard work.
Good work.
This is amazing. This place looks like a studio.
Yes, it is.
What are you doing? What are you guys doing?
We're having a welcome back party for Asuka-san.
Here you go.
Thank you.
It's a lie.
I'm a weak liar.
I'm sorry.
How are you doing?
We have an announcement,
We're getting ready.
So I heard Asuka is done.
How is it?
It's been a while since we've met and rehearsed together.
I was nervous at first.
The first day.
I was too nervous the day before,
I thought it might not work.
I think everyone was a little nervous on the first day.
No one said hello to me.
No, no, no, no, no.
I was so nervous.
I was nervous.
But, you know, I was totally nervous.
I had seen you working so hard.
I'm the same way. I also saw your live performance.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry, everyone. I'm busy.
I'm so happy. I'm glad to dance with you.
It's my pleasure too.
So, Asuka, you have an important announcement at the end, right?
That's right.
My graduation concert will be distributed.
Yay!
Tickets for Asuka Saito's graduation concert are now on sale,
The delivery dates are Wednesday, May 17 and Thursday, May 18.
Both deliveries start at 5:30pm and 5:30pm, and the show starts at 6:30pm and 6:30pm.
Repeat deliveries are Saturday, May 20 and Sunday, May 21.
These deliveries begin at 6:00 and 6:00 p.m., and the show begins at 7:00 p.m. 7:00 p.m.
Tickets will be on sale until the start time of the repeat delivery.
If you have time, we would be happy if you could watch it at home while relaxing and having a drink.
Please do so.
I know there are many people who want to come to the show but can't,
We hope to see you there.
The setlists on the first and second days are totally different, aren't they?
Even if there are some of the same songs, they are performed in completely different ways.
So I would be very happy if you could see us both days if possible.
Please do.
So I would like to take over from here.
It's okay. You can stay there.
I want to go home now.
It's certainly a good time.
Thank you for your hard work.
See you at rehearsal.
Good night.
Bye bye.
So, I think it's been a while since Asuka-san's appearance, but I hope you all enjoyed it.So, I think it has been a while since Asuka-san appeared, and I hope you all enjoyed her appearance.
From here, we would like to make an important announcement regarding summer.
So, please make a big announcement.
Please make a big announcement.
I'm going to make a big announcement.
You found it.
Here we go.
Nogizaka46, Manatsu no Zenkoku Tour 2023, please buy it!
Yay!
Summer means tour, after all,
I thought some of you might be interested in the tour,
I guess some of you might have thought that it would be a tour,
We have decided to go on tour again this year.
So, today, I would like to announce the dates and venues of the tour.
Get your notes ready.
Memo memo.
So, first of all, the sheath!
Yes, please.
Please.
Yes, please. Midsummer national tour.
Huh?
The first venue is..,
Yes!
Makuhari on July 1st and 2nd.
No, it's not.
What?
Huh?
E?
It will be held on July 1 and 2 at Makkomanai Akaisui Hymer S Arena.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy. So much.
I'm so happy. It's the first day. This year.
First day? It's the first time.
Yes, it is. I guess I'll talk about it later,
I was happy to be able to do it twice in a row, two years in a row,
That's for sure.
Please come, everyone.
Please come.
Last year was the first time in 9 years?
We had a great time playing in Hokkaido,
It was a lot of fun. It was a lot of fun.
Are you happy to be in your hometown?
I am extremely happy.
It's so fluffy to be able to commute from my hometown,
I see.
It was a very strange feeling.
That's for sure. Everyone was very excited,
Bananaman-san came too.
That's right.
It was in Hokkaido,
He gave us those, right? The sea urchin snacks.
That's right.
I used it and bought it 3 times.
They were so delicious.
I ate a lot of delicious food,
I will be there again this year, so please come.
I'll be there this year. And let's go on and on.
Next, I would like to announce
Seira and Naoto,
Ioki-chan.
I'm looking forward to it.
Where are they?
I will be there.
July 12 and 13 in Osaka at Osaka-jo Hall.
Yay!
It's cute. Your drawings are cute.
I drew the first look.
It's so cute.
I packed Osaka into this picture.
I've already been to Osaka every year.
It's still kind of cute. The Kansai dialect, for example.
It's true.Indeed.
Also, the excitement of the fans is a bit like Osaka,
Osaka is a place of great excitement for fans.
They have a lot of fashion.
Indeed.
Because that person is also very fashionable,
He's very flashy.
She's very good at it.
There is a unit called "Obachan" in Osaka.
I'm going to use that as a motif for my painting.
Oh, I see.
How cute.
I'm looking forward to this year's event. Two days in Osaka.
Then, let's continue,
Okay.
Is it Sho?
Yes, please.
I am,
Hey!
What?
I'm sure some of you have noticed this,
This star-shaped face,
No?
Ta-da! It's Hiroshima.
We will be at the Green Arena in Hiroshima.
I think I was there last time, too,
I think I was there last time, but everyone enjoyed the food stalls, like the fried momiji manju buns,
I think we enjoyed the food stalls, didn't we?
I did.
Don't you want to do it again this year?
I do!
Thank you very much.
Oh, you're having it again this year? Catering.
You better believe there will be.
Please believe me.
Are you from Hiroshima? It's already complete.
Yes, I am. My feelings are Hiroshima.
That's for sure.
Kyoto is a feeling.
Feelings.
Feelings. Both are feelings.
Yes. I am sorry.
I'm sure you are right. Last year was the first time in seven years that I was allowed to visit Hiroshima.
I ate teppanyaki and all the food was delicious.
It was delicious.
We will continue this year, so please come and join us.
I hope to see you all there. And then, Lilia.
Yes.
What?
No way. Of course not.
Of course not.
Why am I here?
Ta-da!
Oh!
Shopping?
I am the Okinawa Leader in Okinawa, April 22nd and 23rd!
Congratulations!
This is great.
I'm so happy.
I'm in Nogizaka myself for about 7 years,
A dream I've had for over 7 years,
I've been in Nogizaka for about 7 years, and my dream for over 7 years has been to do it in Okinawa,
I'm so happy.
I'm happy.
It's the first time in Nogizaka history. In Okinawa.
Yes, it's the first time. It's the first time.
I wonder how it will be. I wonder how it will be in Okinawa in the summer,
Is it hot? Yes, it is.
It's hot.
You don't seem to like it.
Wait a minute.
But the humidity is not so bad, or maybe the ground is not so humid.
It rains a lot, so everyone should bring sunscreen.
Please have them take it with them.
Is this outdoors?
This is indoors.
Indoor.
This is the new Okinawa Arena.
I'm very happy.
It was built in June.I was able to do it in about June.
I see.
It wasn't there when I was there.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to going with everyone.
Aren't you worried about the catering?
Okinawan food.
I'm also looking forward to eating umi budou (sea grapes).
Pretty specific.
Small things.
I made a mistake.
Small, small, small.
I was surprised.
It is small.
I'm looking forward to Okinawan cuisine.
I'm glad.
I'm sure there are many local people who have been waiting for us,
I would be happy if those who are far away could also come on a trip.
It's a vacation.
It seems to be the number one trending topic on Twitter right now.
Hashtag
Nogizaka46min TV.
Now, let's continue.
It's not over yet.
Continue,
Saku, Ayane, and Ren.
Please come on in.
On August 5 and 6, we will be performing again this year at Nippon Gaijin Hall in Aichi Prefecture.
I've been to Nagoya every year, how do you like it?
Are you looking forward to it, Ayaon?
I am looking forward to it, and since it is in my hometown, my relatives and family will be there,
I'm also looking forward to the food in Nagoya, which is delicious.
That makes me happy.
How about Saku?
I am happy. I am happy to be in my hometown.
Also, there are a lot of people here, so there are a lot of people who are the same as me.
I feel reassured when I go back home.
But, you know, the three of us are going to make it exciting.
Yes, you know, you can speak up, too.
That's right.
I'm just here.
It's been a while, right? You've been vocal.
That's true.
Last year, you said it was in your heart.
This year, I can do it, so please look forward to it.
Next, Kubo and Rika.
Please come on in.
On the 14th and 15th of August,
Akasugi Heim Super Arena in Miyagi Prefecture.
Yay!
I'm so glad to hear that we will be there this year as well,
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy. It's in my hometown.
I'm really happy.
I'm really excited.
It goes up.
There's a lot of good food here. I'm kind of excited.
Tohoku people come to Tohoku,
Like squid.
That's for sure.
That's right. I have a lot of family and friends who come,
Many of them are very warm,
I am really happy to be able to experience my hometown,
I am really happy to be able to go again this year.
I'm very happy.
Let's eat beef tongue.
Let's eat.
I wish they would abolish only the beef tongue tickets.
Please. Really.
Let me eat as much as I want.
I want to eat it.
I'm looking forward to it. Let's do our best.
Yes, I will. So let's continue.
Is my hand the last one?
Then, Yoshiki Yamato, please.
Se-no!
Boom!
Don!
Meiji Jingu Baseball Stadium from August 25th to 28th.
Yay!Yay!!!
Look at the schedule, everyone.
This year's event will be held for four days in a row.
Four days!
How do you like that?
That's amazing!
We all need to start building up our physical strength now.
For sure. Muscle training.
Really.
I mean, let's do strength training.
I picked up muscle training. Sorry.
I'm looking forward to it.
How about the rain?
I thought it was raining really hard.
It rained a lot.
But you know, last year, Manatsu-san was a very rainy woman,
There were a lot of senior members who were rainwomen.
But everyone seemed to be a sunny girl,
But the 3rd term students seem to be more like rainy girls.
I think they will be fine. If everyone drinks with me, it will be fine.
Everyone will be fine.
As long as you support us, we'll be fine.
That's why I love rainy days at Jingu,
But there are four days, so you can enjoy it in all kinds of weather.
I hope it will be fine.
I'm looking forward to it!
So, I've announced all the dates,
Let's take a look back.
Here it is.
The tour starts on July 1,
The last day will be the 28th.
That's about 2 months.
That's great.
But the first day is a little over a month away,
So it will be soon?
So it will come really fast.
That's fast.
Just a little bit.
That's right.
So, I guess there will be 16 shows in all. I hope to make the best summer memories with you all,
I hope to make the best summer memories with you all,
Wait a minute.
Please look forward to it.
So, the ticket selection will start on Sunday, May 14.
This Sunday.
So please check the official website for more details.
Okay, Ayame.
Now then, Ayame.
Please tell us about your enthusiasm for the tour.
Yes, I am.
This year, we are going to tour all over Japan from north to south,
I want to make as many people as possible fall in love with Nogizaka,
I am also looking forward to the tour,
I like to get closer to my seniors and juniors,
This year, I don't want to use my shyness as an excuse,
I want to talk to them more and more and get to know them better.
I am happy. Let's have fun.
Thank you very much.
Next, Lilia.
How's it going?
Yes, it's great. I was really happy when I heard about it for the first time,
I was really happy when I first heard about it,
Not only the members but also the staff are really looking forward to it,
We are really looking forward to it, not only the members but also the staff,
It may be hot in Okinawa in summer, but I will do my best to make the venue even hotter,
It may be hot in Okinawa in the summer, but I will do my best to make the venue even hotter.
I am so happy.
We are able to do this in Okinawa because of Lilia's presence,
Thank you so much. Let's have fun.
And Sheath.
Yes, I'm here.
How is it?
Yes, I think so. I couldn't hear your voice last time,
I'm really looking forward to hearing the cheers of the people in Hokkaido for the first time,
I think I was able to make last year's event more exciting,
I think I was able to make last year's event more exciting than the previous one, so I would like to make this year's event even more exciting and make Hokkaido hotter.
Last year, they appeared in a lot of TV programs,
I hope to make this year's event even more exciting than last year and make Hokkaido hotter,
Let's all do our best again this year.
So, today, we started with Aska's interactions with the various members, and then there was the announcement of the tour,So, today, we started with Aska's interactions with various members and even the announcement of her tour,
Asuka-san's concert is next week?
Oh no!
But we really rehearsed a lot today,
It's been a while since I saw Aska-san dance,
She has always been a person who has cherished live performances very much,
Seeing Asuka-san dancing after a long time, I felt a lot of things,
I would like to send them off in the best possible way,
We want to send them off in the best possible way, so we will do our best with all our energy,
I would like to do my best with all my heart and soul, and I would like to make the tour even more exciting with momentum from there,
I want everyone to enjoy the tour and have fun,
I would like to make this a tour that everyone can enjoy and feel the goodness of Nogizaka,
So please keep your schedules open this summer.
Let's have fun together.
I hope everyone can enjoy the tour and feel the goodness of the Nogizaka. So, that was just a short time ago,
Let's all do our best again this year,
Let's all do our best. I hope you had a good time.
Everyone was so cute.
So, let's all work hard for Asuka's graduation and the summer tour!
Hey!
Yes.
This way.
That's all for this edition of 46 Minutes TV.
Thank you all for watching until the end.
See you again sometime.
Bye bye.
See you soon.
Good night.
Good night. Thank you very much.